Visit turkision.com for more!
I will never forgive you!
Do you understand me? Never!
You wouldn't want that.
But you hurt me!
Would I hurt you, huh? You were going to
say yes to Mehmet in front of me!
I thought you would throw
that ring at Mehmet's face!
But what did you do,
Holofira? What did you do?
You were almost going to say yes to Mehmet.
Holofira... Don't you love me?
It doesn't change anything.
You abducted me twice!
If you do the same thing,
I will abduct you again!
Orhan! You don't understand!
You don't see the truth!
-Come on, tell me! Tell me! What am I missing?
-The truth is...
...our lives are different!
There is only one truth in my life.
And that is standing before me now.
From now on, you won't go to the
frontiers marketplace! We will get married!
Orhan! Orhan who does not know his limits!
You won't behave, huh?
You won't behave, Mehmet.
Gonca... Tell me...
Aren't you going to say
something? Why are you silent?
Do you.. -No.
Alaeddin..
I mean... -Brother!
Brother!
Sister... what happened?
-Brother...
My Orhan brother abducted
Holofira from the marketplace.
Mehmet Bey went after them
with his Alps. My brother is alone.
Bad things will happen if
we cannot find them, brother.
Come on! Come on!
I will come with you!
My Allah, protect them...
Beys... Do you think I used the
Bannerless to have you killed?
Tell me..
You are here, right in front of me.
Tell me, what could have stopped me?
You are planning your games
under a shadow, Osman.
No Alp would stand next to you...
...except for the Bannerless.
If you are genuine with
your words, open the door!
But you are making it difficult.
Are you in the lands of enemies, Karasid Bey?
You know how hospitable
We will have dinner together!
But only Allah knows what is
going to happen after that meal.
It was not good that you left Vasilis behind.
You can plan a game and
take him back, Crusader.
In the end, he is alive. Did
you bring what I asked for?
I did.
The tax you asked for.
I thought we were together in this.
What belongs to Erlik Khan is only his.
Glorious Mongols don't depend on anyone.
But you depend on me.
What about the weapons?
Lords were informed. They will
prepare all of them and send the caravan.
Byzantium's army will protect it.
You are a smart man, Crusader.
You are working with the right person.
Commander, Beys gathered in Osman's city.
Osman and Yakup's sons
were seen in the forest.
Let's go and kill them. -There is no need.
I have the sword. You
be Ayhan. Do your politics.
Confuse them and turn them into enemies.
Then I should go and do my duty.
Nokers! Come on! -Take the gold.
Come on.
Your Alps must have killed the Bannerless...
...already, huh, Osman Bey?
Walk! Move!
You drew your swords
against the great Beys of Turks!
Now... You will either surrender...
...or I will destroy you all
with the order of Osman Bey!
Dastards!
Move! Go!
The leader of the warriors
and the people is the Bey.
How dare you set a trap against Beys, huh?
And as if it was not enough, you
said Osman Bey ordered you to do so!
And you tried slandering huh?
Boran! Aykurt!
My word is the swords of my men!
You will learn the cost of doing this!
Wait, my Osman Bey!
This is the letter we received.
It says you sent it.
And we did our duty.
Turkmen Beys who are deficient in
obedience will arrive in Yenisehir tomorrow.
You will shoot them on the road.
There is not even a seal on
it. Which duty are you off to?
Whoever did this treachery..
Will pay for this.
Was there no traitor in
your palace, Osman Bey?
It seems this is not the only one.
The rest, those who
heard you calling the beys..
Planned trickery to set us against each other.
-Shamil.
-My Bey.
-Take them to prison. I will have them answer.
-As you command, my bey.
You will know what it means
to swing swords to Turks, move!
Osman Bey.
Why did you call the beys? Even
without their Sultan's knowledge?
It is now apparent.
I do not accept your sultanate.
My mercy is not infinite, Osman!
Mine as well, Yakup Bey.
I don't have much patience as well.
Both against enemies and against
those who help the traitors among us.
-What will we do now, Osman Bey?
The drums of
war will be played.
-A field will be prepared.
-Osman Bey.
Stop dreaming.
What will we do against Mongols,
whom defeated many states?
We are a hand, that can not even unite yet.
Will we challenge Mongols?
This is a independence fight
Yakup Bey, it won't be easy.
Even if we are few, we will prevail.
However, know this. It won't be you..
Who will lead the army.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
You did wrong Orhan, wrong!
-Now who will save you from my hands?
-Shut your mouth.
-Get out of my way, Mehmed.
-Holofira.
-Do you want to go with Orhan?
-Enough! I don't want to see both of you!
-I said stay behind me.
-Holofira doesn't want to come with you, Orhan.
Let her go.
Holofira came here with me^
she can leave only with me.
If you want to take her, you
have to go through me, Mehmed.
Alright then. Come and
I will destroy you, come!
Who will destroy who?
If there are some who will
choose the path of peace..
After my father Candar Bey
became martyr, I am not with them.
When Osman Bey said council, guessed it's
a council of war, so I brought the army.
I will be with Osman Bey.
There is a Bey of Turks, long live.
How many alps do you have, Suleyman Bey?
Your father used to not do
anything without counting.
-You get eager very easily.
-Death..
Does not differ those who count
from those who does not, Yakup Bey.
Seven thousand of my
alps is ready, Alhamdulillah.
Alright, alright.
If Osman Bey deploys ten thousand horsemen..
You can walk to death together.
The first duty of a Sultan
is to keep his people alive.
I won't let you break my people.
Pull yourselves together.
Since Osman Bey wants to be obeyed,
wants an army under his command..
It is not something that
can be decided hastily.
There will be a council at
frontier marketplace tomorrow.
Everyone will think about it.
Then declare their decision.
You are correct, Yakup Bey. However,
it will not be at frontier marketplace.
It will be at a secret place that I will say.
I will let you know the place.
So that neither the infidels..
Nor someone from us will set a trap.
There is no more trickery,
Osman Bey. Whatever happens..
It will happen face to face. An
eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
As always Yakup Bey. As always.
Alps! Stop!
Brother, don't do it! Stay calm brother!
-Alaeddin move away.
-Brother, what are you doing!
Move sister, move! Orhan will
learn his lesson today, move!
-No!
-Who will learn lesson..
-Who will not, we'll see!
-Enough!
I said enough! Enough brigandry.
Children of Osman and Yakup.
You bark a lot. However you won't bite anyone.
We will take hatuns out of this place.
I won't go. I won't run anywhere brother.
I will not leave you here.
Sister, don't you see there is a
lot of them. This is not an escape.
You will call far back up, quickly!
-Sister, come on! Gonca come on!
-Quickly Gonca, quickly!
Come here.
Come here. The wolf's tooth wants your blood!
Come on!
Allah is the greatest!
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Malhun Hatun.
Orhan Bey doesn't want this, obviously.
Before everyone talks about this...
Listen to me, girl. I know you have pride.
But this won't happen again. I will handle it.
What will you handle Malhun Hatun?
How could he abduct a girl from my market?
Saadet Hatun, nobody abducted any girl.
Don't make rumors.
Making rumors would damage only my house.
The girl your son took
on the back of the horse...
...is the girl who my son is going to marry.
Patience... You should pray that your
son won't make anything treacherous.
If something happens to my son,
Treachery is what you know best.
What you have done is a cause of war.
-Saadet Hatun.
-You are deceiving this girl.
Your son is running after other girls.
Hear your words, hatun!
Erlik Khan has presented his
wrath. Demons will bite your soul!
Come.
When I take your head, this game will be over.
We can't resist! We should retreat!
Brother! Archers! Draw back!
-Come on, Orhan!
-We're going back into the woods! Come on!
Fathima.
Mother.
-Mother.
-What happened? Where are your brothers?
-Mongolians attacked.
-What?
Gonca. Holofira, are you alright?
My brothers and Mehmed Bey
are repelling the Mongolians.
-They are too many, mother.
-What are you saying?
Alps, go help Orhan Bey! Come on!
Alps, you too! Quickly!
We're going to Yenisehir.
We should let them know.
Let's go inside the tent.
We will be safe there.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Suleyman Bey settled in the
inn you mentioned, my Bey.
-He's resting.
-Good.
He says he supports you,
my Bey. But will we trust him?
He helped us in hard
times. We will trust for now.
Those who know you, both trust you
and want to share your dreams, my Bey.
What else could we do?
Tell me. Any news from the spies in Konya?
We'll get new information
before the sunset, my Bey.
We also placed watchmen
in the frontier market, my Bey.
If Allah permits, we will learn
where the dog called Veysel is.
Alright, alright. Tell
the army to stand on alert.
Suleyman Bey has come all prepared.
We will prepare the army too...
...so we can encourage the
beys to prepare their armies too.
Osman Bey! Osman Bey!
If you are to recruit an army, I'm here!
Nobody can go to battle without me!
Look at him!
Oh Ghazi... Ghazi...
Just wait. Wait, Cerkutay.
Ghazi, listen.
It's difficult to be an alp.
Are you well trained?
Test me, Osman Bey.
You say so? Okay.
Alps, everybody go to their duties!
Ghazi and I are going to train.
-As you order, my Bey.
-Sure, my Bey.
As my Bey orders.
Come on, Cerkutay. Come on.
Give it to me.
Show mercy for your Bey.
Come.
If archers hadn't come, I
would have killed that dog!
Orhan, enough!
If you hadn't taken Holofira away,
we wouldn't have faced the enemy.
-Mehmed.
-Brother!
Brother! Mehmed Bey! Stop.
They're surrounding us.
The dogs smelled the blood. We need to go!
For the blood of my nokers
you will bleed much more!
By that time, you will have no blood left!
-Come on!
-Let's go!
Commander Karacelasun.
We've got news from Tabriz.
Good.
I'm sparing their lives for
the sake of the great news.
I got the position that I've been
expecting from Emir Coban.
I'm the governor of Konya now.
Great Mergen, play your drum
which is the melody of Tengri.
Let's entertain the dark souls.
-Peace be upon you, Dervish.
-Peace be upon you, too.
This is the second time we have come across.
You're coming from a fight again, obviously.
Join us. Let me check your wound.
The wound isn't important. But I will be glad.
But I'd like to learn your name this time.
-Join us first. Let me check the wound.
-Thank you.
Ya Shafi (The One Who Cures)
Thank you Dervish Effendi.
You have started fighting
against the infidels,
but it seems the battle inside
of you is giving you a hard time.
On one side, my love...
..on the other side, my mother.
Without her permission...
..I don't know how can I
do this, Dervish Effendi.
It's like Uways (Q.S), is that so?
Our people call him Uways al-Qarani
(Q.S), he had the same trouble.
Uways (Q.S)
is someone who was in
love with Rasulullah (PBUH).
Sallalahu Alayhi wa Sallam.
He longs to see him just once.
He wants to go to Madina,
but his mother is an old woman
she's blind and has no one but Uways (Q.S).
She gives him one condition.
She says go but return quickly.
Do not visit anywhere but
Rasulullah's (PBUH) house.
Uways promises her mother to return quickly.
He sets out and gets to Madina.
He goes directly to Rasulullah's (PBUH) house.
But Rasulullah (PBUH) is not at home.
Uways (Q.S) gets so sad but
he also promised his mother.
He explains the matter to Hadhrat Aisha(R.A.).
He sends regards to our
Prophet (PBUH) and sets out.
He goes to Yemen. When he
explains the matter to his mother
his mother prays for him and says "You
couldn't see our Prophet (PBUH) in this world,
may you see him and be his
neighbor in the afterlife, if Allah permits."
On the other hand, Rasulullah
(PBUH) comes back home,
and asks Hadhrat Aisha(R.A.)
"Aisha, who came here?"
Hadhrat Aisha (R.A.) explains the matter.
Rasulullah (PBUH) says that
"His test was to keep
his promise to his mother.
He kept his promise and passed the test.
He couldn't see me in this world but
he will be my neighbor in the afterlife."
Uways (Q.S), for the sake
of his mother's approval
he left it to the afterlife, but
he was rewarded with a great reward.
So, there are lessons
we need to learn from it.
Even being rewarded with a prayer of Prophet
requires the approval of your mother.
Yes, of course.
But there's always a way to
get your mother's approval.
You did not tell us your name, but
you healed us with your words again.
The realm of love, a sacred place
Ancient, eternal, love's embrace
The sayer of love's tender word, is
the tongue of power, by all, heard.
The One Who speaks is Him
The One Who hears is Him,
The One Who sees is Him,
The One Who shows is Him
He is the One Who speaks every
word The image is a station of the soul.
Image in blood speaks graceful words,
Within the blood, the words turn into action
The image found its voice to say
The voice paves wisdom's way.
Images in the shadow's frame,
Voice alone can't rise to fame
one can't act without the blame,
it is the essence of message.
This is our lover's wine, this is our flavour,
The rose of the sherbet
of love that we entwine.
You tell Him about Him, it is Him, He
is the One Who says it, the word is His
He is ours, we belong to Him, From now
on, it is the glorification of the tongue.
Yunus' words sound severe,
The unbelievers fail to hear,
One immersed in a life of wrong,
misses the recognition of Allah
You... Dervish effendi?
Are you Yunus Emre, the owner of these words?
Our Rabb is the One who
makes me say these words.
This poor man is the Yunus of Tapduk Emre.
He is the Dervish of Tapduk Emre.
That's why they call him Yunus Emre.
We were under the shadow
on the shore of a river
-but we were not aware of it.
-Astaghfirullah.
My Sheikh would say "the one who kisses
one's hand kisses his own hand as well."
e will stay under your shadow,
do you allow us, Yunus Emre?
Astaghfirullah.
They're here, Shahzades are here, Orhan Bey
Alaeddin Bey is here!
Stop. Come here.
Welcome, sons.
-Thank you.
-My son.
-Orhan Bey. -Welcome.
Thank you, my Valide.
Thank you, mother.
Are you wounded?
No, no I'm all right.
All right then.
Look at you. What's the matter with you?
-Nothing, mother.
-Yes.
-We'll talk about it.
-We will.
Very well, your sons are
back. Come on, I'm hungry.
-Are you hungry?
-Is that so?
She's so hungry!
Sons, stop it. Leave my daughter alone.
What's going on here? Come
on girl, have a seat. Shahzades.
I hear about what you
do. Don't do those things.
If you keep doing it
you will pay for it heavily.
You shouldn't play with
him. Do not act without orders.
Come on, let's have a seat.
Here.
Come on.
That's enough, Bey Father.
I'm so tired of my brothers.
Have them marry with someone
so their women would tolerate them.
You're babbling again.
Let me get married too, Osman
Bey. I'll take Gonca Hatun!
Hey! Tawba, tawba.
-Who does he act like?
-How should I know?
Sit down, Ghazi.
-Sit down and eat.
-Why would I?
Eat the good foods, come on.
Ghazi Alp, do not disobey your parents
just to get married.
But Ghazi Alp is smart.
He does everything to convince his mother.
That's right, you want Gonca Hatun too, right?
-I don't want her.
-What?
Gonca is a daughter of a
Bey. Why would she marry you?
Maybe she already found a son of a Bey.
What? Did she? Did she find someone? Tell me!
I'll tell you about it, have some patience.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
We had to cooperate with Orhan
against the Mongol dastards, my Bey.
But our hostility continues.
Then do what needs to be done, Mehmed.
He will do it, of course.
He will marry Holofira.
This will ruin Orhan.
Keep us out of it, Hatun. You deal with it.
Mehmed has other things to do.
Osman... Osman, Osman, Osman...
Osman can do anything to be the leader.
Today, all the Beys were almost
going to pledge allegiance to him.
I postponed the council just in time.
The council will be set again tomorrow.
Kanyumaz. -My Sultan.
Send presents to all Beys.
Tell them that we appreciate their loyalty.
Yes my Sultan.
Mehmet. You go and bring that Veysel dog.
Let's not go to that council with empty hands.
We will take Veysel's head there.
Can I come in, my Sultan? -Come in.
My Sultan. Ayhan Agha is coming.
But they are crowded,
they have horses and carts.
What happened? Let him come.
Alaeddin...
Tell me. Is the fire in your heart...
...still burning? Or did it turn into ashes?
Look... Your sister is
trying hard to marry you off.
There is still time, father.
Ooo, my Shahzade.. If I were your age...
..I would marry Gonca Hatun right away!
Ghazi... Ghazi... What are
we going to do with him, Ulgen?
We are in trouble. Open
your mouth, my son. Open it.
Eat, my lion. Eat..
What are we going
to do with him, Ulgen?
Look...
Make him eat, it will keep
him busy. He must not talk.
What about you, my
Shahzade? Will you also wait?
If my father and mother allow...
...I do not want to wait, Ghazi.
Q’sdeeeoe.
My Osman Bey, my Malhun Hatun,
why don't you let Orhan Bey get married?
Ghazi Alp... Mothers-in-law
deal with daughters-in-law.
Bey fathers do not interfere.
Can I come in, my Bey? -Come in.
-Come.
-Thank you, my Bey.
It's important.
Kay iFamilyTV.com THE LEADING
TURKISH SERIES PLATFORM
My sons.
Alps. Come with me.
Come on.
I came here for Veysel.
What are you saying, Ayhan Agha?
If you allow me, I want to say a few words.
If you allow me, my Sultan..
...I want you to cut that dog
Veysel's head off with this sword.
Did you come all that way
to say this, Ayhan Agha?
With this sword, my Sultan...
...Crusaders martyred my
friend who I called "my brother".
I want revenge, my Sultan.
I want to cut his head off, my Sultan.
The world of Islam...
...is the da'wah of all of us, my
Sultan. May Allah make you believe...
...I suffered for so long because of
those dogs of Byzantium, my Sultan.
And I heard something
really important, my Sultan.
That dog named Veysel that traitor...
...is important for the Crusaders.
I know. I know. -What will crusaders do...
...to save that dog?
I wonder how many Lords would...
...give up on their treasury for
that piece of devil... But, I know...
...revenge is more important for you.
For revenge, you will reject the Lords'...
...treasury, for sure.
Ayhan Agha... Revenge...
...can also be taken without taking lives.
For some, gold is more
important than their lives.
Maybe... taking their gold...
..will hurt the infidels more.
But, my Sultan... We should
behead that dog! For a great Sultan...
...why would gold be important?
-No.
Since that son of the devil is worth a lot...
...let's not waste it. Tomorrow...
...we will give Veysel to Crusaders
and take their gold in return.
Ayhan Agha... You are a trader.
You will mediate.
You will tell the Crusaders what we want.
And during the exchange,
you will stand next to Mehmet.
Go now. Safely.
Yes, my Sultan.
Father... Do we need gold?
We will have caught two
birds with one stone, Mehmet.
We do not need gold, but...
...we need to get rid of all the infidels.
We will destroy them all. And Osman...
...and all Beys will see
the sultanate of Yakup Bey.
Yakup Bey...
...did not kill that dog named Vasilis.
How and why, my Bey? His
carelessness turned into betrayal.
My Bey, allow me to go...
-Don't you do that.
My son... Don't.
We will not be deceived like them, brother.
Making a move before finding out
their intention will be wrong, my Bey.
My sons.
Tomorrow, you will go to the
frontiers marketplace with Alps.
If you see Vasilis alive..
...you will kill him and leave without
showing mercy to anyone...
including Germiyan and Crusaders.
Yes my Bey.
Alright... But...
There is more. I received
news from our spies in Konya.
Tabriz assigned a new
Mongol Governor for Konya.
They are getting ready under great
pressure. They even agreed with Byzantium.
They prepared a big caravan carrying weapons.
And they asked Byzantine to protecting it.
If Byzantine's army will protect it...
..it means a crowded and
armed army will be waiting for us.
But we will make our
preparations accordingly my Bey.
That's true. That's true.
Gokmen!
My Shahzade. -What happened, Mehmet?
Were you afraid that I would kill
your man with my arm that you broke?
I am not like Osman or
Orhan who you played with.
I can take your breath away in a second.
In the morning, we will
trade your worthless life.
-Gokmen!
-My shahzade.
No one will talk to him until morning.
-Understood?
-As you command, my shahzade.
We will depart in the morning.
Mehmed.
Didn't I tell you? You can not kill me.
-I am immortal.
-For now..
Shut your mouth. Don't
make me break your other arm.
-Boran.
-My bey.
Send your best scouts to
the caravan route in sunrise.
-Let them do their work.
-As you command, my bey.
As we say, it will be hard.
Of course it will be hard..
So that the reward is big.
There are a lot of weapons on this caravan.
When we ambush the caravan,
take the weapons and hand them out..
Tell me, how much our army will get bigger?
At least two or three times more, my bey.
When armed people start chanting war..
No bey will run from fighting, my bey.
This will allow us to fight in unity.
My bey. Forgive me, however..
Most of the alps will go with shahzades.
-We remain few.
-So?
You know the best, no doubt. However..
Since we have these bannerless..
We only saw harm from them, no help.
Let us have them on the front,
let them be of use for once.
You say so?
-Beys, what do you say?
-It is correct, my bey.
It is a good idea, my bey.
Good, good. However..
No one will know about
the ambush we will make.
-Cerkutay.
-My bey.
Tell beys the location of the council.
I will come there after the ambush.
-As you command, my bey.
Call the bannerless..
To the place where we
will carry out the ambush.
This will be their last chance. Who knows..
Maybe for us as well.
If we can not stop this caravan, then
we won't be able to stop these tyrants.
If we can not have the beys
with us tomorrow, maybe..
It will be hard to even protect ourselves.
However, if we succeed, then..
No one will be able to stand in
our way. With Allah's permission..
We will call the whole world home.
If Allah permits, my bey.
If Allah permits.
My mother. My dear mother.
You are silent. That is the worst.
I know how angry you are at
me. But do not remain silent.
Look.
If it weren't for your prayer,
my road would've been closed.
I know that. And I don't want to go on road..
Without your approval. However..
I can not give up from Holofira, mother.
I understood that very well today. Is
there no way to get approval from you?
I understand you. However,
you did not understand me.
So be it.
I will take Holofira as a bride.
-However, on one condition.
-What is it, mother?
-Tell me, I will get to it quickly.
-Not you.
-Holofira will do it.
-What will she do?
She will become a muslim.
Holofira. Will become a muslim.
Sister, what are you doing here?
Shush, this is the best part.
Since you love her more than your life..
Then so be it. Of course it will be hard.
However, I will teach her
how to be a hatun of a bey.
My mother. My dear mother,
I knew you would accept.
My dear mother.
The love of children comes before all.
Sister, did you hear that too?
-May it be blessed brother.
-My brother.
-It is your turn now.
-I hope so, I hope so.
I got rid of one of my brother,
now it is the other's turn.
Look what she is saying.
Maybe, the time you will get
rid of your other brother is nigh.
-Mother, don't.
-Come here.
You will tell me everything.
-Bala mother, you've heard it, Osman
Bey is waiting for us, we shall leave.
-Come on brother.
-He is waiting for us, mother.
My valiant brother, you saved
me just in time again, thank you.
Holofira, my dear daughter.
This issue is not a good sign.
You have to make a choice now.
lam very confused Saadet Hatun.
I know. I know of course.
I know that this will not work
with Orhan, can you see it as well?
-Or are you still..
-No.
For me, Orhan is no more.
Malhun Hatun is right. We can not be together.
-So you've spoken with Malhun.
-Yes.
She wants me to go.
I understand her. She is thinking about Orhan.
I need to finish this trading business here.
I will leave, Saadet Hatun.
Will you leave, just
because Malhun told you so?
-Don't you have your own order here?
-No.
Not just because of her.
But for Orhan.
My dear daughter.
Who are you sacrificing yourself for.
Open your eyes widely. Orhan is naive.
Both his mind and his heart is naive.
What I am trying to say
is if Orhan's love was true..
They would be arranging your wedding now.
No one, not even Malhun can stand..
In the way of true love. Don't go anywhere.
Stay firm here, near me.
My son has also fallen for you it seems.
I want you to be my bride.
I will think about it.
Now, if you'll allow me.
My Saadet Hatun, Guice has things
to say. She is waiting by the door.
Let her in.
Guice, tell me what happened?
Alaeddin Bey has opened up to
Gonca Hatun. Told her he loves her.
-Alright, and what did Gonca do?
-Gonca Hatun..
You put me in such a spot, scholar..
I don't know what to do.
You on one side, my family on the other.
My Gonca.
-What are you thinking
about, my dear daughter.
Nothing, mother.
Stay close to Holofira. She
will wed your brother soon.
Won't this marriage make things
worse between Kayi and us, mother?
Why would it?
Didn't you say they would
make Orhan marry Aysima?
Yes, but Orhan Bey loves Holofira.
If this marriage happens,
...Orhan Bey and my brother
will be enemies forever.
Then... What you want from me...
I mean... Alaaddin Bey and
I will be enemies, mother.
It's totally different.
When Orhan loses Holofira,
he will turn against his house.
Then things will be as we want.
When you win Alaaddin's heart
...nobody can stand against your father.
Did Alaaddin bare his heart to you?
You wouldn't hide anything from me, would you?
No, mother. Alaaddin Bey doesn't trust me.
-He listens to his mind.
-He will listen to you.
Very soon.
Gonca, if you say you can't
do this, I will take over this.
What will you do, mother?
You will see when I do.
Well... I'm listening, son.
-Mother. I am...
-Yes?
I love Gonca Hatun.
This is not new.
My dear... You finally
confessed it to yourself, huh?
Not only to myself, mother.
I told Gonca too.
Oh... Really?
-What did she say?
-Nothing.
How come?
Doesn't she love you?
When Fatma brought news from
Orhan, I couldn't get the response.
Oh. I see..
Fine. You will get the
response soon, I hope
I hope so, I hope so.
-Mother.
-Yes?
I listened to my heart.
-But my mind is still...
-I know.
I know your fears. I'm
afraid of the same thing, son.
Gonca is a good girl.
But her mother and father are hostile to us.
You say this won't work?
No. I'm not saying anything yet.
It's you who will find out, son.
Neither let your heart blind your mind...
...nor let your mind ignore your heart.
How will I know, mother?
Look into her eyes.
What you see there is the truth.
My lady, you are thinking about
what happened today, right?
Orhan never understands me.
He can't see he and I don't have a future.
But today I saw him so
furious for the first time.
His fury scares me.
Mehmed Bey and he were like
they were going to kill each other.
I'm afraid that's what will happen at last.
A great war will begin
between Kayi and Germiyan.
I feel trapped.
There is only one person
who can get you out of it.
Your aunt. Shall we send her a message?
Never! Never, Alca.
She shouldn't know anything.
My aunt's arrival would be a disaster.
Maybe, I should just go.
I don't think Orhan Bey will let you go.
He will give up only if you get married.
What will your response to Mehmed Bey be?
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
Alca, this color is beautiful.
-Put this on the front.
-Not as beautiful as you.
No colors are as beautiful as you, Holofira.
Can you get out, Orhan?
I don't want to see you.
I told you that I would handle everything.
Holofira... My mother and
father... They all accepted it.
We can get married now.
-How?
-Look.
I have a duty now. But I
wanted to let you know this first.
We will be together. We'll
be together soon, Holofira.
With one condition, though. My mother...
...wants you to be a Muslim.
Orhan...
How could you want me to do such a thing?
How could you expect me to change my religion?
Holofira, this is the only way.
Orhan.
-Don't expect me to do this.
-For us.
For us to be together.
Where are you, Gonca?
Where are you?
-Alaaddin.
-Gonca.
Thanks to Allah. I was
afraid I might not see you.
Afraid?
What are you doing here?
I'm going to a mission.
But before I leave
..I want to hear your response.
-Here? Now?
-Yes.
Gonca.
Alaaddin, let's go.
You will wait longer for
the response, Scholar.
You are playing coy, huh?
Fine. So be it.
Coy hatun.
-Take care of yourself.
-You too.
May Allah keep you safe.
Today is the day to show
the power of Germiyan...
...to Osman and all the other beys.
Who supports the dog called Vasilis?
What spies did they place among us?
You will reveal all of these!
And then kill them all.
Mehmed, your victory...
...will my biggest leverage
against the beys in the council.
Today, everybody will see...
...Osman Bey is just talking...
...and Yakup Bey is being a Sultan.
Alright, father. Both Vasilis...
...and those coming to
take him will face our wrath.
All the preparations are set.
-Where is Ayhan Agha?
He let Crusaders know
about the place of exchange.
I told him to join us on the
way. He will be waiting for us.
Alright then. Stay safe.
May Allah bless your fight, son!
May you have a safe journey
and a strong sword, son.
Thank you mother, keep praying for me.
We will be victorious and they will be ruined.
There's no other way.
Right on time, Crusader. Tell me about it.
I tricked Yakup so bad
that he didn't kill Vasilis
-to sell him to Crusaders.
-Is that why you made me wait?
Yakup tricked you.
He wouldn't change his mind
about killing Vasilis to take gold.
Of course, Karacelasun.
Yakup will want to use
Vasilis to find the power
behind him and destroy
that power, old wolf.
So they are not going for the
exchange, they are going for war.
They are going for war.
While they expect to see
a small Crusader group
they will find Commander
Karacelasun, his nokers, his soldiers
and my men. They will find a huge army.
It will be their last battle.
Good plan, Crusader.
But you attract suspicion.
Astagfirullah.
You'd make even the devils jealous.
If your plan works one day,
we will form even more alliances.
It will work, Mongol.
I've never felt Jesus Christ
so close to me.
We're starting.
Raise your head.
Raise your head!
Don't you hear Osman Bey? Raise your heads!
How could you be so terrible enough
to think that I would attack the Beys?
Osman Bey, we...
We know that you want to lead.
You want to kill the Beys
and be the only power.
A state cannot be established by
killing the people of your own blood.
It would only destroy you.
How could you be so vile
enough to believe this order?
We were exiled, Osman Bey. We have
always been attacked by our own blood.
Bannerless ones would only
know the bannerless ones.
But thanks to you, we are learning it again.
You will learn it. You will learn it for sure.
This is your last chance to live.
I'll attack and you
will go first.
Yes, Osman Bey. We didn't live like a
soldier but we want to die like a soldier.
Allah knows that.
We have found the caravan, my
Bey. They are going towards Altuntas.
But there's worse.
Mongol dastards are gathering there
my Bey, there are too many of them.
It seems they will make the exchange there.
My Bey, excuse me
but we may not get another chance to hit them.
We will hit them, Bayindir. Those
swords they have will be their death.
Alps, come on. Take them too.
Swords.
These swords are made of the essence of iron.
They have only one purpose and it
is to make Turks live the doomsday.
Gold.
Bring food, let's split our food.
Let our friendship be permanent.
We will kick the Turks
out of this land together.
I miss her a lot.
Who do you miss, Ghazi Alp?
-Who do you think? Gonca Hatun of course.
-Ghazi!
That's enough, you keep saying Gonca.
I don't want to hear her name again.
Already jealous and
acting like a mother-in-law?
Look at him. You'll see
how I act when I slap you.
Let everyone know that Gonca Hatun is mine!
Shut up!
Ghazi Alp will be upset.
Today Alaeddin brother
told that he is in love
with Gonca Hatun.
-Really?
-Yes, keep it as a secret.
You didn't hear it from me, all right?
Otherwise my Alaeddin brother would ruin me.
Sure, I didn't hear it.
I wish I hadn't heard that.
What am I going to do now?
It would be worse if I keep quiet,
but who am I going to talk to?
There's no other way.
If I don't say it, they will
ruin my Alaeddin Bey.
Beys!
Are you bargaining without
the Bannerless ones?
Where is our due?
One of them is Crusader
and the other one is Mongol.
What do they know about due?
We have no choice but to kill them.
For the intruder we offer death.
Nokers!
Attack!
So you came to see the doomsday
before it broke loose, Osman.
You are the one who
must be afraid of Qiyamah.
Qiyamah is the ultimate
union for us. Come now.
There are always valiants who will stop the
infidels on the lands they think they rule.
Come now!
This land is a homeland to friends,
graveyard to enemies!
Come... Let me take my revenge on you.
Your poor lands will be
watered with blood, Osman.
These lands were watered with Turks' blood.
This is how it turned into a homeland.
But you cannot even reach this land.
Stand up. Stand up. You can even...
-No...
-For Karacelasun's drop of blood...
...Ilkhanid will punish you, Osman.
Is that so? Come. Don't run. Come.
Come. Look at me.
Karacelasun became the
Ilkhanid's Konya Governor.
He can be a governor or a Sultan!
An oppressor is an oppressor!
And we never show mercy on the cruel!
Make him stand up.
My Bey... We have the weapons.
-Alright.
-My Bey.
Byzantium and Mongols will
stop for a while after this raid.
No... Bayindir. It won't take long.
Karacelasun became Ilkhanid's Konya Governor.
They won't stop. They will attack.
It will be harder than before.
-What is your order, my Bey?
We will be quick. Make your preparations.
-Take all the weapons
and share with other tribes.
Yes my Bey.
Now the decision that will be
announced by the council is...
is even more important.
If they stand next to us...
...we will have a chance to win.
But if they fall into carelessness...
...then, may Allah help us.
Aameen my Bey. -Come on.
Gonca... Something is different about you.
Nothing's different.
-There is something.
You said we would be companions.
I shouldn't talk about it while struggling
with so many problems, Holofira.
Please, tell me. Besides, I want to
think about something else if I can.
Is it about Alaeddin Bey? I can keep a secret.
Alaeddin declared his love.
I am so happy for you, Gonca.
But I couldn't give him an answer.
I am so confused, Holofira.
-Right.
Your families...
Right.
It is impossible. You were
going to say that, right?
Tell me... Is there any chance of
achieving the impossible, Holofira?
Believe me, I don't know, Gonca.
That's what I ask myself every day.
What does your heart say?
My heart...
...says, "If Alaeddin defeated his mind...
...you can also do it."
I love Alaeddin.
I love him so much.
Then go and talk to him,
Gonca. Fight for your love.
Do you think so?
You? What about you?
Orhan Bey loves you so much.
He asked me to become a Muslim.
If I become a Muslim, his
family will let us get married.
What do you think about it?
I don't know, Gonca.
I don't know.
Gonca Hatun! Gonca Hatun!
Gonca Hatun! -He arrived.
Gonca Hatun! I missed you so much Gonca Hatun!
-I missed you too, Ghazi Alp.
Gonca Hatun! -There is someone waiting
for you behind the marketplace, in the woods.
-May it be easy, Aysima Hatun.
-Thank you.
What you do is really hard.
In the end, they won't let you marry Orhan.
What are you saying?
Everyone is talking about you.
They say "Aysima is such an honourless girl."
They say "She couldn't
put this girl in her place."
I know what to do to her..
You see that necklace?
It is Orhan Bey's gift. You
are just having a dream.
Orhan won't look at you.
So, Aysima Hatun, you cannot reach the power..
...you want so much.
I can.
I will be a Bey's Hatun
no matter what happens.
All of you will see.
Have you no shame, hatun?
-What are you saying?
-You..
Why are you still wandering around my fiance?
Know your place, or
I will teach you.
Who are you threatening on who's
land? You will go away from here.
-You will leave Orhan alone.
-You can not tell me what to do.
Holofira, Aysima. What are you doing?
I did what is needed Malhun Hatun.
No one, I mean no one can touch me.
Aysima, what is going on here?
Holofira. You must apologise to Aysima.
Holofira is not the one that
should apologise, it is Aysima.
Ayhan Aga. If these crusader dogs
do not keep their word, it is on you.
No way, my shahzade. They
were alarmed after hearing Vasilis.
They should be here soon.
You, the dog from prison in Kestel!
Hadhrat shahzade, I brought your gold.
Bring Vasilis.
You waste of the devil.
Heartless Mehmed. You are
giving him for gold, is that so?
-I wouldn't expect that, even from you.
-What shall we do, my shahzade?
-Should we get on them?
-No.
Not now. We will wait.
This gold is enough to claim many cities and
castles even, however I do not want it.
I want something more valuable. The head
of the tyrant is more important than gold.
I want your life! Alps!
Not only Vasilis, but they
will also destroy his superior.
Yakup Bey is playing big, brother.
Correct.
Erlik Khan, send your wrath!
Gazabini gonder!
Feed the flames of vengeance!
Shahzade of Yakup. Today, death is your guest.
My shahzade, I had no idea. I don't
know where these barbarians came from.
You're under this as well, you mongol dog.
And, where are you Alaeddin?
Are you playing trickery again?
-Gonca Hatun.
-Ulgen?
What are you doing here?
I called you here, Gonca Hatun.
You are waiting for Alaeddin Bey but..
I know the tricks you are doing to him.
-What are you saying, Ulgen?
-I thought you were different.
However, you are just like your mother.
No, you got it wrong.
I've heard it all, Gonca Hatun.
-What happened at the palace?
-Osman Bey.
Will go to someone called
"Karacelasun". Their numbers are few.
Alaeddin was supposed plan a route.
You got close to Alaeddin Bey
just because your mother told you to.
You told her about Osman
Bey going to Karacelasun.
How can you do this to him?
Did you tell this to Alaeddin?
My shahzade can not handle this.
If I tell it to Bala Hatun,
there would be war.
I still came to you.
If you have even a small amount
of reason, you would en these tricks.
-Ulgen, you do not know anything.
-What I know is enough, Gonca.
If you do not end it, I will
talk with Shahzade Alaeddin.
-No.
-This is my last word.
No, Ulgen.
Ulgen. What will I do?
Come here, come!
Come on now.
Master, take care as always.
-Be careful.
You would die without me, Mehmed Bey!
You envy me! You go wherever I go, Orhan Bey!
Alps, come on
Alps, be careful! Good
luck! Hit them for Allah!
Vasilis!
Orhan...
I will take your heart out as
the price of my brother's blood.
My father took your brother's head.
You will die just like your brother!
Aysima, what are you doing here?
Speak. What are you doing here?
You invited me.
Liar.
-She's lying!
-Holofira.
Aysima, answer me. Is
Holofira telling the truth?
What are you doing here?
Stop despising Holofira.
What are you talking about, Saadet Hatun?
Nobody despises anyone.
I won't let you insult Holofira anymore.
Saadet Hatun, don't make things harder.
We aren't insulting Holofira. We're just trying
to find out why Holofira slapped Aysima.
If you are looking
for a reason...
Holofira is even ashamed of talking about it.
The one who started this was Aysima.
Aysima, what is this? What did you do?
Let's see you can defend Aysima now, Malhun.
Stop. What you have done
doesn't suit our house, girl.
We're done with you.
My Shahzade!
Gurbuz!
-Gurbuz!
How could you stand against me, Little Man?
This is the death blow!
Celali, let Osman Bey know!
-No, my Bey! I won't leave you!
-Go!
The new governor of Konya seems so cruel.
He will cause many troubles for us.
This land has seen many cruel people.
None of them could stand here.
He will also lose his head soon.
Battle can't be won by talking.
We don't even know who he is.
As soon as he came, he worked with Crusaders.
He organized a caravan. Did you know that?
And Osman Bey who is crying
for battles hasn't been around!
Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you, too.
Where have you been, Osman Bey?
We're struggling with troubles.
But Osman Bey who talks about
armies and battles isn't around!
Do you even want us to
fight beside you, Osman Bey?
You don't know about the
caravan or anything else.
Osman Bey... You have
an explanation, I hope.
-Boran.
-My Bey.
I held the caravan!
I broke Crusaders.
I hit Mongolians!
While you were chatting in the
council, I set up the battle council!
Here is the horseman.
-Horseman?
-Yes, horseman.
Karacelasun is the new governor of Konya.
We all know Karacelasun.
He's not a man to rule from the throne.
The war I have been crying for...
...is at our gates now.
May Allah bless our fight.
-May Allah bless it.
Beys.
If we do what I say
...we will be the winner with Allah's will.
But if you follow Sultan instead,
...we will be annihilated then.
While the matter was so tough
...we pushed you too hard, Osman Bey.
Unlike some,
...you did your part properly.
Forgive me, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey will forgive, Beys.
But let us not make further mistakes.
Everything is clear, we will fight.
You want holy war, is that so, Osman Bey?
I live for holy war, Yakup Bey.
Who are you going to fight?
The current situation is clear.
Let Karesi Bey stand behind you.
Let Felekuddin Bey stand behind you.
Let Suleyman Bey stand behind you.
All of you combined are not
even half the size of my army.
We will distribute the
swords we have to the people.
Everyone who can hold a
sword will stand behind us.
So you say that
you will move towards death
with the Beys and with people.
You cannot resist without Germiyan's alps.
Then it would be a glorious
ending for us, Yakup Bey.
It will not be an end.
It will be a new beginning.
I will give Germiyan Alps under your command.
If you want holy war, I will give it to you.
Just like Tugrul Bey and Cagri Bey.
Just like Bilge Kagan and Kul Tigin.
The throne and council will be mine,
the holy war and hunt will be yours.
The army will be formed, Osman
Bey. You will lead the army.
This is what the Sultan will give you.
If you say otherwise and
say that you will be the Sultan,
all of the Beys will doubt your sincerity.
And I will crush you.
No.
I would have accepted your offer
if I hadn't gotten this bad news.
But...
The hunt is mine
and the council is mine.
And even
if it's not enough, I'll kill you too.
Brother.
My Shahzade.
Give me your pardon.
May my Rabb make you glorious.
No.
Gurbuz Alp, hang on. Gurbuz Alp.
I bear witness that there is none
worthy of worship but Allah,
and Muhammad (PBUH) is His Prophet.
"Indeed, we belong to Allah,
and indeed, to Him we return."
Alaeddin.
My Allah, my Allah help us. Give us strength.
Osman Bey, what are you doing, Osman Bey?
Osman wants power, Suleyman Bey.
Osman wants sultanate.
He doesn't care about holy war or battle.
Shut up!
Shut your mouth, Yakup Bey!
I gave Vasilis to you to kill him.
But you use him to bargain with the infidels.
That's right, I'll destroy
them all with the exchange.
Alps are prepared. I'll ruin them all.
You couldn't do it.
We were ruined, they attacked us.
They killed our Alps. Your son Mehmed...
...my son Orhan are
in the jaws of the infidels because of you.
I did it to capture their leader.
Now Vasilis is alive.
You traded the lives of my Alps
for the life of Vasilis.
-Mehmed.
-Look.
Look at me! You let the enemy escape.
They let them get
stronger, as if it's not enough
the blood of Alps and sons was spilled.
Now tell me.
What should I do to you,
Yakup Bey?
Visit turkision.com for more!